Alice?
Alice, it's you, isn't it?
Yuujio!
Choose your actions carefully.
I have the right to remove up to
70 % of your life if I wish it.
And if you touch me again without my
permission, I will have your hand.
Alice.
Are you sure?
Because it's been a
while since you saw her.
Then we do what she says.
For now.
Now, we can argue our case with her after
we get inside the Central Cathedral.
Enough delays.
Now, Elite Disciple Eugeo,
Elite Disciple Kirito,
you are in violation of the Taboo Index.
I will take you into custody, then
question you, then execute you.
. .
I'm not sure what I'm doing.
I hear a voice that calls you
Do you think you're a star?
I'm going to start with the.
Shining Sun, my diamond.
It's a dream of a dream?
It's time for me, I'll be here!
I'll be here.
Tiese! Ronie!
Lady Knight, forgive our intrusion.
I'd like to return these to our
mentors with your permission.
Very well.
However, I cannot allow these
criminals to carry weapons.
I will look after them.
You have one minute.
Speak with them if you wish.
I'm sorry, Eugeo.
You shouldn't even be
in this mess. I should.
This is my fault.
I was dumb.
I acted so recklessly.
Stop it.
You're not to blame.
You did the right thing.
Your friend was in trouble and
you did what you could to help.
What happened is my fault, not yours.
You have nothing to be sorry
about. Ever. I promise.
Whatever it takes, I'll
become an Integrity Knight.
And then I'll be the one
to come and save you.
And I won't stop until I do.
Till then, don't give up hope.
I swear, I'll save you.
Um, I brought you some lunch.
Make sure to eat it before it spoils.
Thanks, Raiji.
It is time. Step away.
No.
Excuse me.
A robot!
Hey!
You're scaring her, Ichiemon!
What did you call this
thing just now? His name.
What else?
He's Ichie-mon, an electroactive
muscled operative machine, or E-mom.
He's also the first of his type, so
like, we added the Ichie at the top.
Ichie-mon, get it?
And what is this Ichie-mon doing on board?
I'm using it to fine-tune a program and
Higa here is giving me a hand with it.
We're lab partners again,
just like in college.
Good morning.
Morning. You sleep well?
Your problem is its balancer's
processor runs slow.
Can't you buy a faster chip?
It's not like you don't
have the budget to.
Yeah, but cooling and battery
drain would still be a problem.
Considering that, this is
the best that we can do.
One other option would be to tune the
EAP actuator to pick up the slack.
Sure, but the polymer muscles
are last gen, so there's that.
Upgrade to CNTs.
They'll take the strain
better and make it lighter.
We're in our own world over here.
Sorry about the noise.
That's okay.
If Kirito were here, he'd get a big
kick out of this robot of yours.
Actually, we built him because
the Commandante wanted us to.
Wait, Kikuoka did?
What for?
It's a neat idea, actually, but I'm not
sure how serious he is about it yet.
Ultimately, his goal is to bring Fluctlights
from the Underworld into our world.
But the catch is, they're going to
need something they can move around in.
So, wait, the plan is to
put the AIs in... That?
Not this guy.
He's just a prototype for data collection.
We have a second robot with onboard
AI that's way more advanced.
He operates a heck of a lot smoother.
Oh, you don't say.
I wonder what you
decided to call that one.
Niemon, of course! Knee-what?
Oh, right, knee means to.
Anyway, why does having onboard AI
in this other robot make it better?
For us to balance, our brains
make lots of micro-adjustments.
To replicate that
mechanically would take a lot
of tech and a bigger
body to house it all in.
Oh, so if a Fluctlight is
piloting instead of a CPU,
The robot can move more like
a human and also be smaller.
Bingo!
And the smaller the tech inside, the
closer it can look like a human body.
Or so we hope.
For now, he's still a work in progress.
Niemon's coming along, though.
He's looking pretty human.
Well, his silhouette does, anyway.
And maybe one of these days
I'll get to see the damn thing.
Wait, you haven't gotten it to walk
around on its own yet, have you? What?
No, of course I haven't.
His CPU's all loaded up and ready to go,
but no one's home to work the
controls if you get my drift. Oh.
Hey, Asuna. Huh?
Have you had breakfast yet?
No, I haven't.
Then let's go down to
the cafeteria together.
I'd invite Higa, but he already
made plans with Ichiemon.
Bon appétit, ladies!
Back in a bit.
Something wrong, Asuna?
Oh, no, it's nothing. Come on!
We've only been here for a day and
a half, but it feels way longer.
Hey, how you doing over there?
I don't know.
This whole thing feels like a nightmare.
I keep seeing Umber's arm flying
off and Ryo screaming as he died.
Get that stuff out of your head.
Start thinking about what
we're going to do next.
I don't know what that could be.
You know, you're absolutely right.
We have to find a way to break out of this
cell and then figure out
what happened to Alice.
Yeah.
If there's a way out of
this place, we'll find it.
I wonder, did they bring
Alice here eight years ago?
I don't know. Maybe.
Since you brought her up, I just
want to be sure of something.
The night that calls
herself Alice Synthesis 30,
you're positive that she's the
same Alice you're looking for?
Yeah, I am.
Those blue eyes, golden
hair, and that voice.
I'd never forget them.
But she seemed like a
totally different person.
For someone who's supposed to be your
childhood friend, she whacked you pretty good.
But if you want my opinion,
it could be she's under some kind
of mind control or something.
But I don't remember seeing spells
like that in any of our textbooks.
Right, but the high-ranking priests
in the church can manipulate life.
If they can do that, they can
control someone's mind, too.
Although,
if that night really is your Alice,
whose voice did I hear
two years ago in the cave?
Kirito, Eugeo, come and find me.
I am waiting at the top
of the central cathedral.
I will wait there for you both.
Right, you told me that.
When you and Selka were healing me,
you said you heard a voice and then
saw something that looked like Alice.
Yeah, she said she'd wait for us at
the top of the Central Cathedral.
And now we're stuck.
Hey, do you think we can access
the Stacia windows on these chains?
I never even thought to try that.
Give it a shot. Okay.
Whoa, it worked!
We could pull on these chains
forever and they'd never budge.
If we're going to break free of them,
we need to get our hands on a tool
or weapon that's at least Class 38.
Yeah, that won't do anything.
I know what you're thinking,
but the only things we have
in here are a couple of beds,
water skins, and these chains.
A pair of chains.
Yeah, you're right, we got these chains.
Two of these suckers, just what we need!
What?
Hang on, I have a question.
Is your idea to use the
chains against one another?
It totally is.
These chains of ours have
the same durability level.
We'd need something with an object
control authority over 40 to break them.
But if we snap them against each
other, that should wear them down.
Just follow my lead, okay?
Uh...
Ready, and...
Hell yeah!
Not so loud.
You'll wake the guard up.
Let's give it another try.
Ready, and...
I think that knocked at least
a hundred points off my life.
That's a small price to pay
for freedom, wouldn't you say?
Things are looking up.
Mm-hmm.
All right, then.
If we do this, there's
no going back for us.
Remember,
by breaking out of this cell and
looking for the truth about Alice,
or to find the Axiom Church and its laws.
That means from now on, there's no
time for second-guessing or hesitation.
You better make sure you're
prepared for that now.
Otherwise, you should stay here.
Yeah, I know.
But my mind's made up.
If I can return home with Alice, defying
the Church isn't even a question.
I'll even draw my sword
against them if I have to.
I want to make sure that night is Alice,
and if she is, I'll find a way to
change her back to the way she was.
That's the only thing that matters
to me, and nothing will stop me.
Remember what you said on that
picnic with Ronie and Tise?
There are things you should do,
even if the laws say you shouldn't.
I understand what you meant by that now.
All right.
You sound like you're ready, so
let's go give them some hell.
Sweet.
Let's go before the guard wakes up.
Right.
No, no, no.
It doesn't look like anyone's following
us. No way. Look at that. What's up?
Is someone coming?
See these flowers?
I've heard of them.
Kirito, these are roses.
Oh, yeah.
No way!
They are roses.
And this place is chock full of them.
It's rare to find one,
but a whole garden full?
I can't believe we're standing here.
You and I actually made it
to the Central Cathedral.
Yeah, we're criminals,
not Integrity Knights.
But we're here, and
that's all that matters.
It's probably for the best that
things worked out this way.
If we had become Integrity Knights,
we might have ended up like Alice.
They could have gotten in our heads
and screwed with our memories, too.
I wonder if they do that to
all the Integrity Knights.
Do they forget everything
about who they were before?
Who knows?
Yeah, well,
even if a knight's memories
got blocked somehow,
they'd at least remember their parents,
or the place where they were born.
Stuff like that's baked
into a person's soul.
It'd be impossible to swap out those
kind of details with fake ones.
You have a point.
Those fake memories would
likely be tenuous at best.
What if they were flying around while on
duty and came upon the place they grew up?
Once they saw it, they would know,
and all their memories would come...
What?
Not again.
I get it.
You're worried I'll find a way to get my
memories back in that tower, aren't you?
No.
Well, a little.
Would you relax? Don't!
Stop it! Let me go!
Man, I told you before not to worry.
and I meant it.
Whether I get my memories back or not,
we make a great team so we're sticking
together till the end.
Stop treating me like a kid.
It's not that I don't
trust you to keep your
word.
You've only mentioned it
a million times so far.
But when I think about how our journey
might be coming to an end, I feel...
I don't know.
The fact is, it's gonna end. One day.
But don't forget what
that's going to mean.
You'll get Alice's memory back, and
then you're going to take her home.
There's another good thing
that'll come out of it.
You'll get to pick another calling.
It might last the rest of your life,
so you better start thinking
about what you want.
I think I still have a
bit of time to decide.
I know whatever I pick won't have
anything to do with woodcutting.
No surprise there.
Come on, let's get going.
As expected, I have to admire
my Lady Alice's wisdom.
Everyone thought escape from
that prison was impossible,
and yet my mentor predicted it. Mentor?
She ordered me to camp out here for the
night in anticipation of your breakout.
To be honest, I was skeptical you'd
show up, and oh, how wrong I was.
An Integrity Knight.
His mentor is Alice.
That said, you'll be returning
to your gloomy prison shortly,
after I administer punishment
for your transgressions.
You've been warned, so prepare yourselves.
Well, here's a warning for you, then.
If you think we're gonna go back
there without a fight, you're crazy.
Such nerve.
In honor of your bravado,
I shall introduce myself.
I am the Integrity Knight
Eldrie Synthesis 31.
I do not have a territory to my name yet,
as I was freshly summoned
only a month ago.
I do hope that fact doesn't bother you.
I will be able to give up my
eyes. I can't make my hands.
I'm not going to leave you.
I will be able to keep you.
I need you.
I have no fear.
I have
no fear.
I have no aquela care of my wounds.
I haven't found my neck.
It's not your frame.
I'm not your eyes.
I have no sense.
I've been around the corner.
When I feel like you are.
I haven't seen the chakra.
Even if I can find the
saudon. I have a little bit.
I think I need to be in my body.
May I list you?